welcome everybody to the 2017 yugioh
championship
we are just mere seconds away from the
first match of the day so my homeboy who
do you think is going to be victorious
here I mean [ __ ] I gots to go with the
old man on this one woman can't do [ __ ]
maybe if this was a cook-off
she could make some sandwiches but it's
not this is a duel a battlefield for men
I agree still who would have thought the
duelists would be these two Queen Aleena
the mother of last year's champion
facing off against her own brother Uncle
Chuck it appears the match is about to
begin
everyone hold on to your butts
let's lure which here we start we plug
in on a card in defense mode a Yenta
meter
I'd like to understand he left his
monster open for an attack he must be
planning something oh well it doesn't
matter I have everything I need to make
him my [ __ ] I am afraid to say that it
is over for you Charles
summon magician of faith in attack mode
a only 300 attack points goaaaaal Irina
attack if you're whatever just oh I'm
not done just yet
by using the effect of silent magician
from my hand I am able to swap it with
my monster currently on the field
okay that's what it is the yo-yo got zip
and now for silent magicians effect
silent magician gains 500 attack points
for every card in my hand go silent
magician attack his monster bless me
poor lemon are you okay
now I will finish by playing two cards
facedown
oh man it looks like Queen Aleena sure
has Uncle Chuck on the ropes this is a
great duel so far Jarro know something
something isn't right
he must win everybody is watching me
earth of the cards read em if akina's
row done that's our chip guilty
guardian' toe defend Somali protect me
Celtic guardian
why the hell is Celtic Guardian in an
elemental hero deck bro
I thought you helped Uncle Chuck build
his deck last night well I tried to but
he told me to go [ __ ] myself
can't Yossarian death-metal hit OMB with
pleasure silent magician you know what
to do
[Music]
you don't deserve to work clothes not in
front of me I'm gonna be partying nobody
can run for me yeah Charles the Hedgehog
it looks like it's over for me soon it
was a pleasure fighting by your side no
today I stole this from me wait those
over you know look at them lowly
charging for the next hack the moment
I'm hit by that [ __ ] I'd beets and
stretchy the [ __ ] graveyard but it's
not over yet you can still beat the
[ __ ] ass just believe in the heart of
the cards they're ready to fire Charles
stand back I'll take it out there you're
and they do exalt echt your life points
now go well go on show me what you got
[Music]
ah
you